ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4265
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files
1997-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lawler, Edward J.
Smith, Robert S.
/4265
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
8060039
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4070: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional /4161: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4175 G: ILR School Dean's Office 50th Anniversary Exhibit Panels /4193: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4194: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4194: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4290m: ILR School Dean's Office Memorial Statements /4293: ILR School Dean's Office ICCD Records /4325: ILR School Dean's Office Course Descriptions
Lawler, Edward J.; Smith, Robert S.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office
8060039
- Stat. Dean's Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Statutory Affair 98-99, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Confidential, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Statutory Dean's Mtg., 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Statutory College - Spr. 199, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Academic Deans, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Academic Deans' Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Academic Deans 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Academic Deans' mtgs. 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Academic Deans mtgs. 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)